Home About Resume Trainings & Workshops

Arun Siddappaji

DOWNLOAD CV

arunsisu@gmail.com

Experience Summary

20+ Years Experience in Software Testing, includes, 10+ Years Management Experience. Excellent skills in Building and Mentoring Engineering teams across Domains. Experience in building talented engineering teams including Managers, Leads and Senior Individual contributors. Experience in managing talented team working across technologies – SAS, RAID, SAN, File Systems, Storage Management, Server Technologies, Operating System Internals & Virtualization. Successfully managed large complex Software Releases for quality. Excellent collaboration skills with direct team and team across the globe. Excellent interpersonal skills working with Program management, product management, Development team, Architects, Operations to develop and execute project and organizational strategies. Successfully managed team delivering end-to-end solutions. Person with passion on People Management and Mentoring.

Experience

Company	Peak Position	Period
● BROADCOM ° connecting everything •	Senior Manager - Test Engineering	May 2011 to Jun 2018

Expertise Demonstrated:

Project Management, People Management, Customer Engagement, Budget Management, Contineous Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Management.

Company	Peak Position	Period
vm ware	Project Manager - Test Engineering	Jun 2008 to May 2011

Expertise Demonstrated:

Project Management, People Management, Budget Management, Contineous Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Management

Company	Peak Position	Period
(intel)	Project Lead	Oct 2005 to Jun 2008

Expertise Demonstrated:

Project Schedules, Risk Assessment, Project Reports, Quality Management, Contineous Team Efficiency Drives, Cross-Geo Interactions.

Company	Peak Position	Period
sasken Make the Right Connection	Technical Lead	July 2005 to Oct 2005

Expertise Demonstrated:

Project Deliveries, Schedule Management, Risk Alarams, Project Reports

Company	Peak Position	Period
PACKARD	Senior Engineer	Feb 2000 to Oct 2003

Expertise Demonstrated:

Project Deliveries, Schedule Management, Risk Alarams, Project Reports

Education

Institute/School	Year
Sri Jaya Chamarajendra College of	1994
Engineering, Mysore University,	-
Mysore	1998
	Sri Jaya Chamarajendra College of Engineering, Mysore University,